beautyexpert.com 2015-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Beauty Expert | Free Delivery

This site uses a VeriSign SSL123 Certificate to offer secure communications by encrypting all data to and from the site. VeriSign has checked and verified the site's registered domain name.

We are committed to protecting our customer’s privacy. We are entirely open about our information gathering practices. Please take the time to review this notice which states our privacy policy.

For us to process your order, we need to know your name, email address, delivery address, credit/debit card number, security code and expiry date. We will not collect any information about you unless it is specifically and knowingly provided by you. The information we collect will be accurate and up to date. You can check this at any time by contacting our customer care department. We will immediately correct any inaccuracies you report.

Additionally, we will look at the products you buy, together with the way you view our site to enable us to send you information about products and services that you may be interested in. We will use this information to tailor your view of the site to make it more interesting and relevant in respect of the products and offers on view.

We collect information about our customers via server logs, cookies, order forms and competitions. A cookie is a file that your web browser places on your computer’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings. The cookie does not store any credit/debit card information nor password details. Please see our Cookie Policy for further information.

We have business and technical partners whom we share data with to handle orders, process credit and debit card payments and provide a range of services, including for fraud protection purposes. They are bound by Data Protection covenants and must process the personal information in accordance with this privacy policy. You should be aware that if we are requested by the police or any other regulatory authority investigating suspected illegal activities to provide your personal information, we are entitled to do so. 

In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.

We may also use your data, or permit our group companies to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by email. If you do not want us to use your data in this way, please change the settings in your account. Replying to the 'unsubscribe' link in promotional mail will also ensure that your name is removed from our mailing list.

This website employs industry-standard SSL to provide secure communication (including for credit card transactions). SSL is a communications protocol for transmitting private information over the internet. It works by encrypting data that is transmitted over the SSL connection. When you place an order, your personal details (including credit/debit card information) is encrypted and then sent over the internet using an SSL connection. No one can read or access the data that is being transmitted.

It is important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your password and to your computer. Ensure that you log out when you finish using a shared computer.

In addition to the company's safeguards, your personal data is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act (the 'Act'). The Act requires us, as registered Data Controllers, amongst other things to ensure that the data we hold about you should be processed lawfully and fairly. It should be accurate, relevant and not excessive. The information should, where necessary, be kept up to date and not retained for longer than is necessary. It should be kept securely to prevent unauthorised access by other people.

We take the risk of internet fraud very seriously. With the volume of fraudulent credit card transactions increasing, we make every effort to ensure all orders are thoroughly checked using the information already supplied. There is a possibility we may contact you to make additional security checks and we ask for your co-operation to enable us to complete them. Fraudulent transactions will not be tolerated by us and such transactions will be reported to the relevant authorities.

## Contact Us

If you have any queries on any aspect of the above policy, please [contact us](https://www.beautyexpert.co.uk/beautyexpert/customerQuery.account?action=postQuery&skeletonAccount=true).
